Meet the world's only loveable billionaire.
Arthur is a comedy, romance film directed by Jason Winer.
A drunken playboy stands to lose a wealthy inheritance when he
falls for a woman that his family doesn't like.
Arthur, played by Russell Brand.
Hobson, played by Helen Mirren.
Naomi Quinn, played by Greta Gerwig.
Susan Johnson, played by Jennifer Garner.
Vivienne, played by Geraldine James.
Bitterman, played by Luis Guzmán.
Arthur is a 2011 American romantic comedy film written by
Peter Baynham and directed by Jason Winer.
It is a remake of the 1981 film of the same name
written and directed by Steve Gordon.
Its story follows Arthur, a wealthy and alcoholic philanderer who, after a drunken run in with the law, is forced
by his mother to marry Susan, a suitable spouse, or else he will be stripped of his inheritance.
But things suddenly become complicated once he meets and falls
in love with a free-spirited woman named Naomi.
It stars Russell Brand, Helen Mirren, and Jennifer Garner.
The film was produced and distributed by Warner Bros.
and was released on April 8, 2011.
It grossed $12.2 million during its opening weekend and $48.1
million worldwide, against a budget of $40 million.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of new york city, chauffeur, nanny, romcom, playboy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.